Thank you for watching!
After this, I would like to thank all the people in my to the people in my house, to the people in my house, to the people in my house, to the people in my house, to the people in my house, to the people in my house, to the people in my house, to the people in my house, to the people in my house, to the people in my house, to the people in my house, to the people in my house, to the people in my house, to the people in my house, to the people in my house, to the people in my house
my heart is pounding my heart is pounding my heart is pounding
I'm so excited to spill the sparkles
I'm thrilled to see their smiles
Hearing your voice and breathing
Yugas the letters letters letters
I'm ticking, ticking, ticking, ticking
I feel like I'm overflowing
I'm alive, that's what it means to be alive
I'm feeling so good
Before I knew what it felt like
I was invincible
I need to cool down a bit. I'll call it what's in front of me
Sunny, sometimes cloudy, sometimes cloudy, at night it's a cold, sometimes icy...
What is this weather, stupid? Is there such a thing?
I'm so excited!
I'm so excited for you.
I'm so excited. I'm so excited. I'm so excited for you.
I'm getting more and more into you.
I'm falling in love with you more and more.
I'm so excited because of you.
Thank you for the thrill.
Tell me it's not so bad.
Canyon Town.
I can't remember a time
I can't remember a time before I knew what this felt like.
You know, if you want to know the future, that's the one.
You know, that thing you see on the Internet?That thing you see on the internet.
I like him, I like him, I mean, he's close to my heart.
I think I'm getting set.
What?
That's a love reading.
What's going on?
I'm so excited!
Oh, my God!
I'm so excited... for you.
You, you, you... give me more and more and more and more and more and more
I'm in love with you, I'm in love with you
I can't stop it.
I want you to look at me in a special way
I want you to change I want you to be there for me
But then our eyes meet
I can't take my eyes off you. I can't look down.
Not because I'm in a bad mood, but because I'm embarrassed.
I keep looking in the mirror and acting this way.
I have to tell myself that.
Calm down.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm so crazy about you, I'm a total mess.
I want you to make me feel good.
I'm crazy about you, and I'm a failure.
I love you so much, I love you so much, I hate you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I hate you so much
I love you so much, I love you so much, I hate you so much, I love you so much
I love it so much, I love it so much, I love it so much, I love it so much, I love it so much
I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love...
It's so cute!
Even if there's a grain of rice on it...He said there were rice grains on it.
He's so cute.
Where are you today?
Come on. You're all mine.
Cute, cute, cute. I love you.
Cute, cute, cute. Kiss, kiss, kiss for everything.
Anything.
I can forgive anything. It's a crime to be cute.
Matching keys, matching key chains
Every day is an anniversary.
Who's calling you? You better answer the call.
It's not cute to be mean.
We're in this together, aren't we?
Geez!
So cute! So cute! Too cute!
So cute! So cute! I can't stop smiling!
Don't make me nervous.
Just look at me.
I love you so much, I hate you so much.
I can't stop sniffing it.
I can't stop loving you, I can't stop loving you, I can't stop loving you
I hate you so much, I hate you so much, I hate you so much
What a lie
I love, I love, I love, I love
I'll never let go
What about you?
You don't have to tell me. I know.
Why can't you give me a better hug today before bedtime?
Why can't you give me a better hug?
I don't know.
I'm so unreasonably angry with you.I'm so irrationally angry at you.
Please don't hate me.
Difficult love
I love you so much.
Sometimes I'm indifferent.
Don't be bothered. Accept it.
Cute, cute, cute, I love you.
I can't stop loving you.
I'm so precious. I'll have you all to myself.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
I'm cute, cute, cute, I like you, I'm cute, cute, cute, I can't stop loving you
It's a sin to be cute.
You're such a sin
Cute, cute, cute, cute
I'm so excited, I'm so excited, I'm so excited, I'm so excited
Ahamon.
Today, I'm going to call Tokimeki Advertising Department, Ahamon.
with super Toki-Sen during the national hall tour
Summer Festival live streaming
Looking back on the live performance
The second half of the tour is also the strongest theory special
Yay!
Oh!
Amazingly long. Amazing.
So,
Rank on the sober hearts!
We are the super excited publicity department.
We look forward to working with you.
Please do.
Yay!Yay!
Today's live stream,
The day of the super-toki-meki green is
I'm sorry to say that I'm not feeling well.
We will be taking a break today.
We will do our best to make up for Hiyori's absence
We will do our best to make it as exciting as Hiyori's,
Let's have fun together today.
Please join us today.
Please do.
Pewley
Pewley.
Cute.
So cute.
Can I introduce myself one by one?
Sure.
Thank you very much.
I'm Kanamin Tsuchino, a.k.a. Kanamin Superiki Miki Brauner.
I'm Kanamin Tsuchino.
Cute registration.
Yes, I'm Kanamin Tsuchino. The super-melting purple.
I am Julico and Anjulia.
Please.
I am Hitoka Osakai, aka Hito-chan, of Super Tokimeki Lemon. Pleased to meet you.
I am Haruka Koizumi, aka Oharu, the super-toki-meki pink.
Oharu!
I am Aki-chan, aka Aki-chan of Chotoki-meki lemon, and Asuke Suda. Please take care of me.
Aki-chan!
So, here we go.So, here we are.
Today, we are already at the halfway point of the current nationwide hall tour of "Cho toki meki seinenbu",
Today is a special live broadcast where we will look back on the live performances so far and talk about the highlights of the upcoming tour.
It's early.
It's the turnaround point.
We've already done 6 stops, right?
Only 4 more stops to go.
That's fast.
I'm scared.
And this time, the live broadcast will be a tie-up with NTT Docomo Homos.
Yay!
So, I have a request for all of you devoted people.
Please tweet about everyone's memories and impressions of the national hall tour with the hashtag super tense ahoge.
We are looking forward to hearing your questions and messages to the members as well as your impressions of the hall tour.
Well then, I'd like to take a look at the chat and Twitter.
I'm here to say that Oharu Oroshi is too cute.
Thank you.
It's cute.
I'm so happy when people say how shiny and glossy it is.
It's so cute.
I get a lot of compliments. I'm so happy.
There's a fireworks show going on in the neighborhood, so I can hear the sound and it's like a festival.
I can't believe there are only four left.
Autumn, twins are so cute.
They're so cute.
I love it.
I guess she's tweeting right now.
I miss Super Ball Arte.
I used to play this.
I miss it.
I played it at the sink shop.I've done it at the sink shop.
Cherish the summer festivals.
You enjoy it.
I miss Yoyo and the like.
It's so cute.
The set is cute.
Even the details are cute.
The outfits are really cute.
Thank you.
It's cute, isn't it? This outfit.
It's cute.
I can only go to the Tokyo show, but I'll do my best until then.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Good luck.
Did you guys buy yukata this year?
Those who did.
Yes, I did.
I bought a yukata from Monoken.
I want to wear one too.
Me too.
You were wearing one. A yukata.
That's right. A rental yukata.
That's right.
Sakusaka.
I want to wear something like a yukata.
I want to go to summer festivals.
Yes, I want to go to a summer festival. Here it is.
I'm in a yukata with a yukata.
It's here, isn't it?
I can only go to the Tokyo show, but I'll do my best until then.I can only go to the Tokyo show, but I'll do my best until then.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I drew the same contrast earlier.
Sorry.
But it's rare.
I got picked up twice.
Special.
So, and in this super exciting publicity campaign,
We have a campaign where you can get a special offer.
This way.
Please enter from this special site,
You can keep your current phone,
You can get 5,000 D-Points and
We will give you 5,000 D-Points and
and an exclusive benefit for the AHAMO tie-up.
We will announce the details of the limited offer later, so please look forward to it.
Wow. The site is up.
The special site looks like this,
It works.
It's amazing.
I'm looking at it now.
It's cool.
Isn't it cool?
Nine days left.
It says "proceed to entry.
All the members are coming out.
They're cute.
That's great. It's easy.
I'm going to get a prize.
Shiori.Shiori.
Here I would like to introduce some of the features of NTT Docomo Ahamo.
Ahamo is an online-focused mobile service provided by NTT Docomo.
Here are five major features of ahamo.
Don.
Don. Don't answer.
The first is a simple one-plan that specializes in online.
Ahamo is a mobile service that allows you to use 20GB capacity for 2,970 yen per month.
You can sign up from the official website, so you can easily sign up at home.
It's easy.
It's good.
It's easy, isn't it?
And, to our surprise, domestic calls within 5 minutes are free as many times as you want.
Weathering is also free.
AHAMOLIFE is a simple one-stop plan with all the features you need to enjoy your life.
It's great.
No complicated and worrisome fees, no minimum contract term, no membership fees, no minimum contract term, no membership fees.
It's just a simple mobile service.
Isn't it great?
Free domestic calls within 5 minutes.
That means I can call Juria as many times as I want, right?
Lots and lots of short times.
That's right.
Lots of morning calls, lots of noon calls, lots of night calls, lots of snack time calls, lots of night calls, lots of sleepy nights.
Okay?
As many times as you want.
With a mouthful.
And, you know, that's one thing,
I'm also happy to hear that zezzaling is free.I was also pleased to see that zeathering is free.
There it is.
That's wonderful.
Now let me introduce the second one.
The second one is that there are no complicated discount conditions.
But there are some conditions, right? You are the one who thought, "What's the point of this?
Don't worry.
AHOME is available for 20 GB for only 2,970 yen, even if you use it alone.
That's amazing.
How much can you watch YouTube on 20GB without Wi-Fi?
It's just a rough estimate,
I can watch about 70 hours in a month,
That means I can watch about 2 hours a day.
That's quite a lot.
This is what Junior says, so I am sure.
You can rest assured.
You can trust us.
And thirdly, for those who use more than 20GB, we offer a Home Large Volume option that allows you to use up to 100GB.
If you take advantage of the large-size option, which costs an additional ¥1980,
You can use up to 100GB for only 4,950 yen.
Isn't that great?
It's amazing.
You can watch a lot of YouTube for about 11 hours a day.
That's great.
A big serving is a good word, folks.
A big serving.
Happy.
And the fourth thing is this,
If you are worried about the communication speed, don't worry.If you are worried about communication speed, don't worry.
You can use the same 4G and 5G communication as at Ahomoa and the other locations.
There is no speed limit depending on your eye zone.
So, you can upload your SNS immediately.
Thank you very much.
I am in a good mood.
You can watch YouTube with no worries.
Take a look.
And the fifth and last one,
Free international roaming up to 20GB.
Ahomoa also offers up to 20GB of free packet communications in 82 countries and territories overseas.
No need to carry around a bulky Wi-Fi router.
You can easily set it up locally with your smartphone.
It's amazing.
I don't have to worry about traveling abroad,
I'm going to aim for a special overseas expansion in the future,
I can keep an eye on Indonesia in the future,
It's perfect for me.
And, since there will be special offers only available in collaboration with the special selection, please visit the special site,
Please visit the special site.
Thank you very much.
Today's distribution will be a live summer festival distribution,
Ta-da!
It's a festival.
I think everyone already had it in their hands,
It's like a summer festival.
It's great.
Well, let's have a toast first.
Let's have a toast.
I'm glad.
This way.This way.
This is next.
I'm going home with a Ramune and orange juice.
It's summer.
Is everyone ready?
Are you ready?
Well then, thank you for your hard work on the first half of the tour.
Let's enjoy the second half together!
Cheers!
The great July sizers are flowing!
The July sizer is coming, exactly.
And it's a perfect sizer.
It's great! Yum! Yum!
Yum! Yum!
Can I go ahead and eat it then?
Yes! Yes!
You're free to eat this today.
While you're eating.
Let's look back on the ongoing
Looking back on the Heart Roku Hall Tour
While looking back on the Hall Tour 2023
Let's eat together!
Let's eat!
I'm so happy!
Keep up the good work, everyone!
Please tweet with the hashtag super-toxenarm!
We'll be looking at everyone's live memories
Please tweet a lot after this!
I'll be waiting for you!I'll be waiting!
Then, Yuka Rin will take Mizuki Watanabe.
Watanabe Mizuki!
I'll keep her warm.
I'll keep it warm.
Then eat while you're at it.
Let's eat!
What?
I want some! I want some!
Wow, thanks for the watermelon!
I don't know what you want.
What do you want?
Oh, it's coming up.
You want to go this way?
Oh, it's open.
Yeah, it's open.
Sweat.
Are you okay?
Oh, I'm so happy.
I'm so happy.
I'm so excited!
I've heard on Twitter that some people are going to switch as soon as the distribution is over.
Thank you so much!
But it's great, isn't it?
It's really great.
Isn't it too good value for money?
This service is perfect for the specially selected people who are going to Indonesia.
It really is.
Well, fine then, let's have it.
What would you like?
Something beautiful, like baby sponge cake.Beautiful, I guess, like a baby sponge cake.
Chopsticks.
What?
Chopsticks, please.
I don't use them yet.
It's delicious.
May I?
Thank you.
I like this one too.
Yum.
Is that a panda?
It's not a panda.
What's in it?
Bon appétit.
He said he's already switched.
That was fast.
Thank you.
I'm...
It doesn't matter what you eat.
Takoyaki
It doesn't matter what you eat, right?
So cute
Jeriah, you should try some too.
This looks so good!
I've been after it.
Jelia's been after this for a long time.
It's got tomatoes in it, right?
It's got tomatoes in it.
Broccoli?
Bon appétit.Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Jelia, we have squid.
We have squid.
She wants squid.
Yum! Yum!
Yum! Yum! Yum!
It's got basil.
It's not basil.
Wow.
Infe spider 1957 in a sentence.
Pow!
me
Cherry Blossom Festival is here!
Food delicious!
The Corlando response worked!
They are seriously considering switching to the amazing Armon!
Dao, you'll love this!
What? With a fork.
You want to spin it?
Oh, hi.
You two beside me.
I've had some great local food.
I'm telling you, Pamblin'.
It's liquid butter. Who wants to make it?
You want to make some?
Okay, Jerry, I'm gonna go get some squid while you're at it.
It's super delicious.
It's blue.
It's almost ready.
It's blue?Is it blue?
That's amazing.
That's a great color.
Are you waiting?
Waiting.
Don't be afraid.
It's blue, guys.
Isn't it going too fast? There's so many of them.
Oh, my God.
It's done.
We're waiting for rain again.
We're waiting for the rain again.
The closer we get.
The closer we get, the more it looks like there's a lot on the outside here.
It's true.
Top 3 souvenirs from the first half of the tour
Ours?
I got something.
You guys bought oyster sauce in Hiroshima, right?
I want some cucumbers!
You said you wanted some kyurin, so I'll give you some.
Why can't you make more?
It's so tiny.
A little more.
Put some more in.
Maybe I didn't put enough.
Squid.
I got two.
Let's go, Chiria-chan.
We're doing cotton candy. I'll take one of the money.
Then let's sit here.Then let's sit here.
I'm finally going on the Osaka tour. I was so happy to hear Lemon Juice, my favorite band.
It's been a while since I've done that.
Lemon Juice.
It smells like squid.
Want some?
I knew it. Craftsmen are great.
I went to Hiroshima and Osaka.
It was my first time in Gyosei and it was a lot of fun.
Thank you for taking me to so many places.
It was my first time to see someone in Kagogawa.
I was so happy. I'm so happy.
Please listen to what I have to say.
Okay.
Oh, oh, oh!
They're here, they're here.
I had Fab write on my Osaka okonomiyaki.
It's delicious.
It's written in fab on okonomiyaki.
It's true.
I didn't know they could do that.
I want to spoil it, but I'll hold back.
It's delicious.
Action-in-saw-dance.
It's kind of pass, pass, pass.
Is there any more sugar in this?
There's no sugar in it.
Want some?
There's more.
Do you have any more? Sugar.Do you still have it? Sugar.
Cotton candy. The end.
We're done.
Let's finish what we have.
Okay.
Can I put this in?
Put it in.
It smells like squid.
Looks delicious.
Squid is delicious.
It's delicious.
Julia.
Squid.
Squid is delicious.
I didn't think they would play Princess in Miyagi.
Surely, a daily guest of the day.
The daily guest of the day.
I'm going to do it and enjoy it.
The Fukuoka show was the first time I attended this year's tour, but I couldn't resist and went to the Sendai show as well.
It was too hot, but it was a lot of fun.
It was also very satisfying to hear the biggest show of July in July.
Indeed.
It was amazing. I'm waiting for it.
It's because it's July.
I can't do this.
So many first-timers for sure.
It smells sweet, so it's good, right?
They say they're going to do it from now on.
Delicious.
Well, I'd better get going.
There's something next to me on the right side of my field of vision that's been giving off an incredible presence,There's something next to it on the right side of my field of vision that's giving off a strong presence,
May I? There's a noodle shop. Actually.
Nagai Somen.
That's great.
I want to do it.
Let's do it.
Can we do it?
It's a good thing we're here.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
Yay!
How long has it been since you've had somen noodles?
I'm so glad.
It's been three years since I've seen Julia.
So you'll just bring chopsticks and that?
I'm so happy.
It's great.
That's great.
Please.
It's going to be fun.
Someone has to play this.
I'll do it.
Thank you.
Let's take it in turns.
Autumn is first.
Thank you.
Of course.
We should turn it on.
Sure thing.
It's done.Done.
Cute.
He said he'd never seen it before.
What?
It's cute.
It's flowing.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
It's cute. It's cute. It's cute.
I like it.
He's cute.
Well then,
I'm going to go for it.
Let's see who wins.
All right.
All right. All right.
Good. Good. Kistelna.
It's hard to be left-handed.
You know what I mean?
Here we go.
Maybe for the first time.
Here.
Come on.
I can't get it.
Oh, don't shake it, Jemin.
You're good.
Ahhh!
I lost it.
It's gone.
I'm ready.
Yes, yes.
Okay, I'll go to the second gym.Okay, I'll go to the second gym.
Good morning, eyes open.
So cute.
The best.
Hoi hoi hoi.
No, no, no.
Ready.
Aaahhh.
It's true that it's very difficult to play left-handed.
I see.
I did it.
Indeed.
I got it.
Oooh.
Sorry.
Looking for it?
What did I just say?
I've been doing a lot of Nagashi Somen at home lately.
Always Nagashi Somen.
You can do it with your hands? That's amazing.
Yes, it is.
So please eat a lot.
Thank you.
Sorry.
I can't get any.
Maybe he knows.
It'll change.
Yay.
Yeah, it's fine.Yes, I am.
Are you always in charge of playing the video, Aki-chan?
I'm in charge of playing and my brother is in charge of taking pictures.
That picture is absolutely adorable.
It's coming.
I want to take pictures around here.
Take the picture.
I can't.
They'll be back soon, guys.
Hurry up.
Good morning.
Take it.
I got it.
Surprisingly fast.
Taken.
Ending.
Hey, it's Gija.
Don't treat me like a child.
I want to flush it.
Flush?
Can I?
Yeah, I'm good.
Thank you.
It's so shiny.
Oh, that's nice.
Oh, my God.
I'm laughing my ass off at L'Abri.
Okay, bye.
Duckoos. - Duckoos.
It's so nice, it's like summer.I like it. It feels like summer.
I can feel it.
I've always dreamed of doing it with you guys.
I can't take it.
Where's Kanami?
What's that? Kanami?
Come in, Kanami.
Hey, Kanami.
This way, they're shooting.
What are you doing, Kanami?
There's some pretty ladies here.
Are they pretty?
No, no, no.
Stop it, they're cute.
This time...
You can do it.
One time, actually.
You're so cute.
No, no, no!
Target practice.
And what's more...
There's this new girl.
If you beat him...
I'll get a fruit platter at the next catering.
I'll bring you a fruit platter.
I'll get it.
We'll just have to go for it.
So have him work hard for this.
I'll bring something for Rio.
Yes, the best
Let's go for itlet's do it!
I'll play rock-paper-scissors.
I'll give it to Kanami.
Of course, of course.
I think I'm a pro.
All right.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Aiko, right?
There you go.
First, let's play rock-paper-scissors-paper.
Aiko, right?
I'm a pro.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Okay, okay.
I didn't expect it from a pro.
Go pro!
Behind you.
Right here.
He's so cute.
Let's all go for it! Let's all go for it!
If we all go for it, we can do it.
Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh!
That's so cool!
What?
Go for it!
I'm in.
Wow! What's that?
One more time!
Here it comes! I'm being gnawed on now!
Oh, my God!Oh my God!
This might be hard!
Again!
Two laps?
One round each.
Next, Jeriah.
Jeriah, pro!
Let's go for it!
I'd like to eat some fruit, so...
I want to eat it!
Go!
Yes!
That was hard!
So close!
But I can't hit it!
Guess who, everyone!
Here we are.
Pull.
Here.
Kachai, did you do it?
How do you hold this?
Is that right?
That's too close!
That's hard!
Okay, let's go.
Surprisingly, it doesn't hit.
I can't hit it.
Thank you very much.
Akichan.
Let's guess already!Let's guess already!
Go, go, go, go!
Cheese.
Ah!
Okay, hold on.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
Okay, okay.
I've done this before.
Did you hit that?
Go for it.
You know how you drink before your body?
If it wasn't for those legs.
Ah!
Hands!
Th Dominus.
You can lean forward now.
There's more.
There's a half-form.
Types.
dj
ana
I'm doing it, I'm doing it.
OK OK, nice!
Congrats to Pio on this one.
Yay!
That's great!
Well, now that everyone's had their fun, let's go back to our seats.
Yes, you're right.
Now Pio has a little smile on his face.
Yes, it does.Yes, that's right.
Good.
Yes. So here we are at the ongoing Super Tokimeki Strategy's Heart Rock On Tour 2023.
I would like to take a look back at the first half of the tour, which has completed up to six shows.
There seems to be a video that summarizes the famous scenes of the hall tour up to this point, so let's take a look.
First up are the Hyogo concert on the first day, the Kyoto concert on the second day of the tour, and the Hiroshima concert on the third day.
Here we go!
Thank you for your hard work.
Yes, so once again, it was a pleasure to meet you all on this tour.
Wait a minute, are you kidding me?
Can we all sing together?
Happy Birthday!
Happy Birthday
Happy birthday to you
Happy Birthday Dear Kana Bee
Happy Birthday to you
Happy Birthday to you!
Canabee!
You are so cute!
That's amazing!
You're so cute! What do you think?
Isn't it amazing? Cannabis.
Surprised? I am!
I'm just saying, why don't we have a publicist right here in front of us?
Call them! Call it in!
And since we're on the subject, Mr. Publicist...
Will you all join me in singing a little?
Happy Birthday Dear
Cannabis.
Happy Birthday to youHappy Birthday
Happy Birthday
Today we go to the court.
Oh, yes!
I straightened it.
How do you like it, sister? Do I look like a sister?
Let's do it!
No, no, no, no, no!
Let's close the reflex legs.
Here we go!
You're not going to budge, are you?
Yeah, let's go!
Let's go!
Let's get it to my house!
Looks like a fairy, with flowers.
Sure, it's colorful.
Cute.
Cute?
You're a cutie, aren't you?
You know, the fluttering ones.
You know the first one, "Catch me"?
Right there, when he hugs Akichan back.
How's that?
Wow!
I love her voice.
It makes me nervous, too.
I've been using it as a reference since we started choreographing.
My dance teacher sent me a free image.
The moment I saw it...
Oh, I'm going to get a hug!
You're so cute!Cute!!!
I'm going to be more of a backhugger from now on.
I'm going to polish it up a bit more.
Here's something to look out for!
Thank you all for your time today!
Thank you for watching!
This is so delicious!
That's it!
It's probably daikon!
I'll start with Cole & Cole Sports
Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum
I Love You
Yay
Performance Game
Yes, yes, yes
If it's here, if it's here, you have to tell me where it's in.
That's right.
It changes every time, right?
It's not a spoiler, is it?
Welcome to the show.
Hello. - Hello.
I like, like, like, like.
I love, I love, I love, I love
I like like like
Likes, likes, likes.
How many others?
What?Huh?
Hmm?
Hiyori's tick-tock, tick-tock.
Isn't that Hi again?
Hiyori.
Hiyori hiyo hiyo hiyo hiyo?
What?
Suki, suki, suki, suki.
Suki-suki-suki-suki.
Oakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyakyaky.
But I love you all.
I love you.
I love you!
This year's star
I have a lot to think about.
I'm trying to be original.
I've had fun with it every time
I write that
They enjoyed it.
Yay!
Oh!
Otaki!
Ohtaki!
So, it was the first day in Hyogo, the second day in Kyoto, and the third day in Hiroshima.
Well, the first day.
Um, that was amazing.
Hiyori calling me a member of the publicity department.
Calling me a member of the publicity department.
It was Hiyogan.
It was interesting.It was fun.
Huh? I didn't have my birthday booked, and suddenly it's all there.
Suddenly.
I'm starting to feel a little nostalgic.
Those onigiri were really good, weren't they?
What? Tabara's onigiri?
Tabara's.
They were so delicious.
We were sneaking them into our wraps on the way home.
I said, "Won't they be gone after the show? I said, "Won't they run out after the show?
I asked if the venue had any wraps. We went to the venue and asked if they had any wraps,
We went to the venue to get the wraps, wrapped them up, and kept them.
And you know what?
I was really hungry, too. I didn't get any.
Give me two!
What are you going to do?
So cute.
I was so happy.
May I?
Ladies and gentlemen, we have a little behind-the-scenes information from the staff here.
What is it?
I don't like it.
Let me read it to you if it's any good.
At the Fukuoka concert, we received churros in the shape of amae covered with powder in the members' colors.
All the members were very happy to receive them.
Among them, Hitoka-san ate the red churros thinking they were tomato flavor.
When she looked them up later, she discovered that they were strawberry-flavored.
When she tried it again, she felt it tasted like strawberry.
That's right.
This is interesting, isn't it?
It's something, you know, I got the churros and they were in the bag.I received a bag of churros.
I ate it thinking that it was tomato-flavored,
I thought that it was indeed a churro with a salty tomato taste,
But then I looked them up and found that they were strawberry on their website,
Hmm? Strawberry? I thought, "Strawberry?
I tried it again, and it tasted like strawberries,
I thought it could be any flavor.
If you eat it thinking it tastes like that, it tastes like that.
That's amazing. It's so rich.
It's so strong. Amazing.
But it was so delicious.
It was so crispy and crunchy.
It was so good.
It was so delicious.
Memories of the fall tour.
Tell me your memories of the fall tour.
Please tell me.
Thank you for all the tweets.
We would love to hear your memories of the fall tour and messages of support for the members.
The hashtag is "ahamode".
Please tweet about it. Please tweet about it.
I see you are already here.
Shall we go?
Let's see the digest video of the 4th day of the fall tour, the 5th day in Sendai, the 6th day in Fukuoka, and the 6th day in Osaka.
Here is the VTR!
Sorry about that.
Please take it back with you.
Nekotaru nekotaru
Yum!
I'd love to eat a cat.I'd love to eat a cat.
This is a TikTok I'm going to shoot today, and for the first time I'm going to shoot a cute memorial with you guys.
Yay!
So we would like to give you a lecture by us now. Great.
Is that okay? Yes!
Chuya-chan, are you ready? Yes!
I'm ready. Are you ready? Yes!
Then let's go! I'll sing. Come on!
Come on!
Cute, cute, shake your skin, shake your cheeks
Cute, cute, cute, those hands.
Oh, it's different.
I can't stop. Love's eyes.
What's that? It's mine.
You're mine. You're mine.
Cute, cute, cute. Too cute.
Cute, cute, cute. Kiss that smile.
I made a mistake. Thank you. Kiss all of them.
I can forgive anything. It's a sin to be cute.
I'm so cute! What a cute space!
What did you guys eat? That's right.
Oh, who wants Thai chazuke?
I want Thai chazuke. I really do.
Then I'll tell you honestly. I'll tell you what happened last night.
Like this. Last night, I ate moving squid first.
It was moving. The squid was moving.
So were we.
And also, what do you call it?
We used to go to a rice restaurant. You know, there are many rice restaurants.
Fish on a plate like this. O-sukkuri?
Or omakuri omakuri.Like making make-believe.
Chawamushi?
Course? Let's go next time.
Fish? It's like this, isn't it?
I found sashimi here.
I shouldn't have asked that.
But we talked about how we'd all like to go again.
Let's definitely go again. I hope we can make up for it.
I was a little relieved. I'm a little happy.
I don't know if I can get it back.
Let's go next time.
Let's go next.
Actually, earlier, when they were saying that we were leaving in one minute, I was told that my name and Nami's are the same as Kyu's,
I and Namin and Kyu were in the same place.
The three of us were giving each other a big hug.
We were hugging. We were hugging each other not with our body together, but with our body together.
Then, I felt a big "aha" moment.
What?
Kanamin gave you a pianochew.
What? What?
And you know what?
There are still faint traces of Kanamin's kiss on Hiyori's cheek.
Is it true?
Let me see, Hiyori.
Oh, what are you going to do?
I wonder if it's still there.
Maybe later,
Wanna see it?
Oh, yes, yes, there it is.
Let me see.
It's got a hard-to-remove link on it called Pinto.It's painted with a hard-to-remove link called Pinto.
Yes, yes, I was wearing a pinto,
The make-up artist was, you know, frantic,
She was rubbing and rubbing and rubbing.
I said, "Hey, I have to rub it off! I said, "I have to do it," and Pia said, "Oh, okay!
Oh, that's fine! He said, "Oh, it's OK!
He was on this stage.
Thank you for watching!
I smell all kinds of perfume.
Oh, wait.
Did you kiss her?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's got so much lemon on it.
Oh, there's... there's... there's... there's...
Oh, this is good.
This one's good.
I'll go with you.
This is it.
Ha-ha-ha.
Hey, I just happened to mention that I did it, so there.
I'm sure.
You were dying on your own. Chew on this.
I didn't go to my death.
Oh, no.
Fireworks, you have to say something.
I do.
Oh, my God. Are you kidding me?Oh, my God. Are you kidding me?
Did he just go to his death?
You just said that. You said it yourself.
Fireworks.
That's what he said.
It was close.
But you were desperate. Even after that.
You rubbed it. She rubbed it a lot.
Hiyori's face was so cute when she was being pushed.
So cute.
Oh, that was fun.
It was really tight and pink.
It was beautiful.
Beautiful! The kind with the pictographs and stuff.
Yes, yes.
It was really pink.
It really was a "tsk" or something like that.
Indeed. It wasn't that long.
But that was going to die.
Well, the people who saw it thought. It's fine as it is.
Which will you take?
Everyone was dying more than I thought.
Yes. Tokimeki Zunda opened in Sendai.
You were saying something like Zundarika for a long time from now on.
You were saying that.
Is there no such thing? Really.
Zunda color.
It's always been green until now?
For the first year? I've been wearing green for the first year.
There have been a lot of pastel green outfits recently.
Like zunda.Like Zunda.
It has changed from matcha to zunda?
Yes, it has.
It's not matcha. It's Zunda flavor.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Then it's zu.
Yes. Okay, let's do it here.
Okay.
And the Fukuoka Campaign Minori team had a delicious meal.
It's delicious.
We ate.
It was like shlava.
Well, we did our best.
Campaign.
That's right. Campaign team.
We worked hard, too, right?
That's right.
Oh, here.
What?
Oh, I got it.
Let me relax in that room.
It's really delicious.
We were saying that we should all go there together sometime.
No matter which radio station we go to, it's really good there.
It's hard to get a reservation.
They said it was because it was delicious.
They told me I should definitely try the squid.
I heard about the restaurant.
When I heard about the restaurant, I thought about it and realized that I had been there once before,
For lunch? Every day?
I found a business card on the corkboard in my room.There's a business card on the corkboard in my room.
What?
The business card of my room.
That's right,
But that means Hito-chan wasn't there at that time,
Yes, I was mad at her at the time.
But I got some kind of Thai furikake as a souvenir.
Yes, I got it.
From the staff.
Then, because it was so delicious.
I've never been to the restaurant before.
But the fish was really good.
It's really good.
The fish was really good. I want to eat it.
I want to eat it.
Okay.
Then, let's go there sometime.
The staff has been talking to me again.
The first half of the tour is over,
The tour costumes worn today are also working hard on the tour with the members.
With the members?
I wanted to write "together".
They are working hard on the tour together.
The petals of the costumes are so delicate that we have to replenish them even after the Osaka show,
But the number of petals is decreasing after each show,
The other day, petals suddenly appeared from the body of someone who was not wearing the costume,
The other day, petals suddenly appeared from the body of someone who was not wearing the costume.
What does that mean?
I will ask the costumes to do their best so that we can survive the tour until the end.
Good luck costumes.Hardworking Costume.
I wasn't wearing a costume,
I wore it before that.
I was wearing it before that, and I was moving around a lot.
When I got up, I looked at the chair and saw a petal on the chair,
Why are there petals here?
It was like they were stuck to my body the whole time.
But by the end of this tour,
I feel like by the end of this tour, I'm going to be without two flowers on my body,
It would be nice to leave them all over the country.
Lights all over the place.
Leave the live people here.
That kind of thing.
But always with glue,
You take it with you, right?
I pick them up and take them with me.
So, if you find it, please report it to us.
Please report it.
Please deliver it.
Please even deliver it to the person who delivers it.
They are doing a great job with the costumes.
Thank you.
It's a cute outfit, really.
Really cute.
The staff did a great job filming the kissing scene. Thanks for the food.
I'm reading your tweets now, so please tweet me.
Thanks for the food.
Nice. Some of you are eating beef tongue.
Looks delicious.
The last time I went.
Good luck with the outfit.Good luck with the outfit.
Thanks for the support.
Good luck.
Tweet everyone.
Flowers are fleeting and beautiful because they fall, right?
That's right.
They might be dead by the time the tour is over.
Flowers.
Looks beautiful.
Q-tan.
You've found a good sign.
Thank you.
Keep on tweeting and tweeting.
Oh, Aki-chan gave me a towel.
Hiyori's towel.
She's wrapping a towel around her.
This is another Gucha-gawa item from the tour.
So cute.
Really cute.
The illustration is cute.
It's cute.
Really cute.
I was currently absorbed in carpets.
I was glad that I was able to celebrate Kanami's birthday in Hyogo.
I was really surprised.
I'm so happy.
The lamb cake was gorgeous.
I was so happy.
I really didn't know. I didn't even soak the milk in a can.
I didn't soak it in the can at all.
I didn't know what was going on.I didn't know what happened.
I guess it's almost my birthday too.
Oh!
Is there going to be an après?
Is there going to be the first live concert in Indonesia?
It's the first live concert in Indonesia.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm going to see you in Aichi. I'll study hard for the entrance exam. I'll study hard for the exams.
Good luck.
Will you come see me a lot?
I'm looking forward to seeing your hair in the second half.
Sure.
A different haircut every time.
I know you're asking me in the morning. What am I doing today? every time.
Last year, on tour or something, I thought up a haircut for the girl next to me.
You did it.
I want to do it again this year.
I'm sure you do. It would be nice.
I want to try it.
Someone posted a picture of Hentaijin.
Hentaijin is delicious, isn't it?
It's delicious, isn't it?
It's too delicious.
Fukuoka. Ramen.
I didn't eat ramen.
I bought a motsu nabe set and ate it.
Yesterday. It was delicious.
Drinking Kamakura cider that Hitoka and Pio gave me for my birthday,
It was so delicious.
I haven't eaten macha in Kyoto.I haven't had macha in Kyoto.
It looks delicious.
After listening to Hanamin's beef tongue story, I ate many kinds of beef tongue, just to be outdone.
I love beef tongue.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Someone has an amazing collection of all the little Nu-chan.
They are so cute.
It's so cute, isn't it?
There's a lock-on free time this time, too.
All the pictures are cute, and depending on the show, I may be close to them,
So please look forward to them.
Now let's talk about your thoughts and memories of the tour so far, one by one,
Does anyone have any?
Okay, Hanane first?
Yes, I do.
As for memories of the tour, for me personally,
I was very happy to celebrate my birthday at Kyoko, and it was the first day of the tour,
It was the first day of the tour, so I felt like I had more energy.
I was very happy.
Also, the atmosphere of the live show was different in each place, such as Sendai and Osaka,
I think I can enjoy the atmosphere of a live concert every time, which can only be experienced on that particular day,
The audience and us are the only people who are there at that concert,
There is no way that the same show will ever happen again,
We cherish each and every live performance,
We cherish each and every one of our performances, and I hope you enjoyed them as much as we did.
And now that the tour is over,
I hope that everyone enjoyed the shows,
I hope that the live shows will be even more enjoyable in the future.
I will do my best, Nakanishi-san.
Bye, Julia.Okay, Julia.
It's pretty hard to believe that I've been around for 6 shows so early,
It feels as if the first day of the show was about two months ago,
But when I look back at the video like this, it reminds me of that time,
But when I look back at the videos like this, it reminds me of that time,
Of course, it is the same in Taiwan,
Of course, it was the same in Taiwan, but I wore my hair differently at every live performance,
Of course, it's the same in Taiwan, too,
The songs change with each venue,
I try to do it with a different feeling each time,
So I feel very fresh and new,
I'm having a great time,
I am quite sad that the tour will end with only four more performances,
But I hope I will have no regrets for the remaining 4 performances,
I hope to make more wonderful memories with everyone I meet.
I look forward to seeing you at the remaining 4 shows.
Yes, Kita-chan. Kita-chan.
There are songs that change each day on this tour, and there are many songs that we haven't played in a long time,
I wanted to play certain songs,
I really like the fireworks in the distance, the two of us standing side by side,
I really like the fireworks in the distance, the two of us finding them side by side, and we hadn't played that in a long time,
So I had to remember the choreography.
I was looking at the picture of the choreography,
Oh no! Wandy!
Wandy!
That's Julia, right? Singing the lines for one night.
Julia is singing.
Then we paired up and had a performance where we looked into each other's eyes and told a story,
The one with the furibun's laughter.
We haven't really spent that much time together yet, so there is a bit of distance between us,
So there is a bit of distance between us.There's a little distance between us.
It's a little awkward for both of us.
I just started choreographing the song, too,
It was the first time we tried to work together on a video,
It was all ad-libbed,
I was copying everything Hito-chan did.
That's what makes it so cute.
I was looking at the old full pair,
I think about how many things have happened up to this point,
But I think every tour is so much fun because we have different memories.
Let's have fun after this.
Let's have fun.
As for me, as a super-tokimeki promoter,
I'm going to a place where I'm going to have a one-man live concert for the first time,
I have a place where I am going to play for the first time as a one-man live, or an area where I am going to play for the first time,
Aki-chan will also visit some places for the first time,
I think it's a unique experience that you can have only on a tour,
As everyone always says,
As everyone always says, it was a totally different temperature and so on,
As everyone has said, each time we go on tour, there is a totally different temperature and a totally different atmosphere from the audience,
Of course, those who have been to many shows will be able to enjoy the experience,
I think that not only those who have been to many shows, but also those who have never been to that venue before are enjoying the show.
Live performances are fun, too,
The live performances are fun, but the members of the promotion department also enjoy eating local food,
It is also fun to see the members of the promotion department eating local food and meeting other members of the promotion department for the first time,
This is something that can only be done on tour,
I felt that the members of the advertising department were also enjoying the tour,
I am very happy to see that.
What about you, Aki-chan?
I am happy to see so many people,
The tour is really good,I still think the tour is really good,
I was the first person to go down to the audience for the first time on this tour during the Rock On! I went down to the audience for the first time on this tour during the free time.
That made me so happy,
It's fun, isn't it?
It was fun.
When I came out from the back like this,
I'm looking at the stage now,
They didn't even notice we were coming out because they were looking toward the stage,
Even when we get very close, they keep looking ahead.
So when I say something like, "Wow," they come and say, "Wow!
That's fun for me.
But, Aki-chan, you said you were in charge of the audience today,
You said you were embarrassed.
That's cute.
I am embarrassed,
But you know, I hope I will be able to grow and develop my singing and new songs on this tour,
I hope that those who came to all of the venues will be able to see how we have evolved,
I hope that those who come to all the venues will be able to see how we have evolved.
I'll be waiting for you.
Thank you.
Now, I would like to read your impressions.
The fireworks made me feel the summer.
The story about the fireworks. He said he likes it because it's a story he can tell now.
Really? It's embarrassing.
You'll be surprised when you see it. I don't know why I'm doing this.
You're acting weird.
You're so floppy.
I was spinning around when we changed seats.
Yes, yes, yes.
I was spinning around and around.It was kind of spinning around.
That's right. Hisa-chan is spinning around by herself, swinging and turning as fast as she can.
He was so good with Julia.
Julia is something,
There's a big difference in tension.
The old choreography is fun.
It's fun.
I can never show them.
I can never show it to the public.
I can never show it.
No, I can't.
I don't want to show it.
That's right.
I participated in Hyogo, Kyoto, Sendai, Fukuoka, and Osaka.
As Oharu-chan said, half of the fun was going on sightseeing tours with my good friends from the advertising department who met up with me there. Thanks.
Thanks.
Rock on! It was so nice of you to come so close to me during my fili time.
I want to go back.
Rock on! Everyone should check their bangs before the show,
for the pictures.
Yes, I know.
I'm the least bothered.
I'll be here for 3 out of the 4 shows.
Thanks.
I'm glad.
I wish I could have seen the fireworks.
You're so cute, naughty Autumn.
When do you think you'll do it?
It was great to see the excitement of the promoters when we did the fireworks or when we played the song of the day.
I was so happy to hear that they were so happy about this project.
But since we often play an old song each day, I think there are many people who hear it for the first time.But we often play old songs on different days, so I think there are many people who hear them for the first time.
Old songs are fun.
It's nice.
It's also fun to predict which song will be played each day.
Predicting?
I'd like to do something like this.
Four more shows?
I'll do it.
At first I thought I could do one of the 10 shows, but now there are only 4 shows left.
I'm getting impatient.
Where should I put it?
Mr. Yokohama.
He said it's fine.
I can't make it to four more shows, so I'm going to join Soul.
I'll be waiting. Soul.
Thank you.
I thought I would actively use the cute Q.
Let's make them do it.
Cute Q.
I'm looking forward to it because I don't know when they will sing a song they haven't done yet. I'm looking forward to Dead Heat.
Do you think they'll do it?
I think we'll do it.
Dictory Story.
I want to do Dictory.
Where's the "Dictory"?
And what else?
AO.
I like the morning of "Kita Kore Morning".
I like North Collection.I like North Kore.
Then, donpiction.
Dompiction.
Gooskapina.
I miss it.
Gooskapaya payapaya gooskapina.
Gooskapaya payapaya.
I like gooskapina when I do muscle training.
It's so good, isn't it?
Mai-san, gooskapina during muscle training.
I can feel it in my body.
I'm doing it with my mom's menu.
So, thank you all for tweeting so much.
And now, the Heart Rock 'n' Hall Tour 202 3 of the Super Tokimeki Advertising Department is in full swing,
Here comes the second half of the tour.
Enjoy.
Let's take a look at the dates and locations for the rest of the tour, shall we?
First, followed by the next time.
Next time is Sunday, August 13.
Next time is Sunday, August 13 at Niigata Citizen's Performing Arts Center.
And the next one is Saturday, August 19.
Tatehiko Yokohama National Grand Hall in Kanagawa.
Then, on Sunday, September 3, at Aichi Nihon Tokushu Tokyo Shimin Kaikan Village Hall.
And on Saturday, September 9, at the Hitomi Memorial Auditorium of Showa Women's University in Tokyo.
We are looking forward to seeing you all.
There are only 4 shows left.
But thankfully, all tickets are solddirt.
Thank you very much.
Please look forward to it.
We'll be waiting.
Okay, let's look at Twitter some more.Then let's look at Twitter some more.
So here is a special announcement about the Super Tokimeki Advertising Department x AHAMO campaign.
We are currently running a tie-up campaign between Cho-TikiMeki Advertising Department and AHAMO.
Please enter from the special site in the overview section,
We have prepared three gorgeous gifts for those who have transferred from other companies to AHAMO with their current phone as it is.
The first one is 5000 D-Points.
We will give away 5000 D-Points to those who participate in the campaign.
5,000 luxurious points.
D-points are great.
I use it a lot.
I'm using it a lot.
And the second one is a special AHAMO tie-up limited edition of Hall Tour 2023 with 6 live photo data of all the members and their handwritten messages.
This is also a gift for those who participate in the campaign.
Don't worry, there will be one for Healy, too.
Don't worry.
This is a very limited offer, so please check it out.
Please check it out.
I want it.
And the third and last one is a special Hall Tour 2023 costume member autographed checkee, which will be awarded to 30 people in a drawing exclusively for the AHAMO tie-up.
This one will be given away to one of the participants in the campaign.
Here is Healy-chan, too.
This is also a special offer only for this time.
Please join us.
Please do.
Entry period is from Tuesday, July 18 to April 31.
Please refer to the special website URL in the overview section for information on how to apply for the campaign.
We look forward to receiving your entries.
And now, an announcement from the Super Tokimeki Advertising Department.
On Saturday, January 27 and Sunday, January 28, 2024, "Super Tokimeki Propaganda Club
in Yokohama Arena One-Man Live 2.in Yokohama Arena One-Man Live 2.
It will be held!
We will make this one the absolute best live performance for the two days as well, so please look forward to it.
Thank you very much.
Is it almost the end?
It will be over before you know it.
I hope we won't see too many of you from all of you.
Thank you very much.
But I'm also thinking of saying stupid twice.
I'm glad. By all means.
Thank you very much.
It's gorgeous.
I'm switching to Ahomo tomorrow.
I'll say it twice.
Everyone.
Because it's limited, right?
That's right. It's special.
It's amazing, like the pretending during the experiment.
Idiots are also the strongest.
Indeed.
That's amazing. He takes a lot of pictures.
He's taking a lot of pictures.
Lots of people.
I'm so happy.
The theory that idiots are the strongest, too.
Yokohama Ari is the strongest.
He's too cute.
Haruka-san sent me the cutest message in the world today, too.
I'm taking my friends to Kanagawa Park to see her in the express Yamasun.
I'm looking forward to it. Thank you so much.
I'm so happy.Glad to hear it.
The rest?
Umedome and Yokohama Ali.
Yokohama Ali.
I know I'm going to Yokohama Ali.
Definitely bring your friends.
I'll be waiting for you. Bring your family too.
Siblings. Relatives.
Ask them if they're sorry they fell in love with you.
Why?
What's wrong?
I hope you like him more.
I'm glad.
I'm happy.
I'm getting more and more keychains.
This is the best memory I've had in a long time.
I'm looking forward to the remaining 4 shows.
Oh yeah...
I heard you invited the kids' Membuin.
Thank you.
A key chain for each fuller.
That's nice.
It's a limited edition.
It was fun, wasn't it?
You were so cute again today.
It was fun.
I'm so happy.
They packed a lot into the show.
He asked me to come back to Osaka.He asked me to come back to Osaka.
I'll be back.
I'll be back. So, it's almost time for the live broadcast,
Let's hear how everyone is feeling and how enthusiastic they are about the whole tour.
Let's start with Kanabin.
Yes, everyone. Everyone.
Yes, everyone. This is a live hall tour,
I would like to spend more and more fun time with you all,
We will perform at full power so that everyone who comes to the concert will be glad they came, have fun, and feel energized by the moon battle,
Let's continue to have a good time together.
Let's continue to have a fun summer.
Thank you very much.
Thank you to everyone who watched the live broadcast.
Actually, we are on tour right now,
We are really having more and more great and happy memories,
And I'm also meeting a lot of new people who are new to this new life instance,
It's really fun. I'm really looking forward to each and every show.
There are only 4 more shows to go,
I'm looking forward to seeing you all for the first time at the remaining 4 shows,
I always say I'm going to see you again,
I hope to have a great time with you all.
I will do my best to fill you with thrill with my best performance,
Please look forward to it.
Thank you very much for your time today.
So, thank you all for watching me today.
We had a great Nagashi Somen (flowing noodles) show, we did Suteki, and we had a great time,
We had a lot of fun,
We ate a lot of sweets like at a festival,
It was a lot of fun and you could feel the summer in the air.
Looking back on the tour so far, I have so many memories that I can't remember,
I have so many memories that I can't even remember,I have so many memories that I can't even remember,
I think that every concert was filled with love.
I felt once again that we are supported by so many of you.
Thank you for all your support.
There are only 4 shows left,
We will do our best to face each stage seriously so that we will not have any regrets,
I hope this will be one of the best memories of your summer.
Let's continue to have fun together.
Thank you for watching us today.
Thank you very much for watching today.
So, we have only 4 stops left on our tour, and that means that I will be touring with this Nui-chan only 4 stops left on our tour.
I am very happy that you all carry the Neko Nui with you and go with me to various places, and I feel as if I am going with you, even though I am not going with you.
Please don't take off your skirts!
I'm sure there will be a lot to do on this tour, so I'll do my best for the remaining 4 shows to bring you the best singing voice and to have fun!
I'll be waiting for you!
Thank you very much for watching today.
It was like a summer festival, and I'm so happy to have another memory with you all,
I'm going to do my best to deliver my love and lock on to the hearts of everyone who comes to all the shows on the tour,
I will do my best so that everyone will want to come back and see us live again.
I'm sure that Hirolyn will do her best too.
So please come to all of our shows.
Thank you very much for today.
Thank you very much.
Then, let's have a last screener now, shall we?
Tweet us your photos with the hashtag "super special aho hair.
Please do.
Carolyn to me because I was your buddy today.
Chick.
Chick~.
Chick.Chick.
This is Yoshikawa Chick.
Carolyn, Carolyn.
Cheeseв
Cute.
Then, continue.
Machu-chan.
Yes.
Next, then, soap bubbles.
Soap bubbles.
Yes. Kerika. They're so cute.
It's heavy. It's pretty heavy.
It's a watermelon.
Because it's real.
It's summer.
How about a cold watermelon?
Yes, that sounds good.
Thank you.
Did you get it?
Next.
It's so cute.
Yo-yo.
There were so many yo-yos.
Ah!
I forgot the good ones.
Next.
What are you doing?
One of them.
You're about to eat it.
Eat it.Let's eat!
Eat it!
I heard something.
Can I eat it?
I'm a melonha.
What's that?
What is that?
I don't know what a melonha is.
Yes, ma'am.
Akichan!
Look!
What is it?
I've never heard of it.
It's so cute!
Look at you.
It's delicious.
It's so cute!
Delicious!
I wonder if I can get six people to scoff.
Let's go.
Which camera?
This one.
With Chihuly and Lucien.
I'll be right here.
Chickenshit.
I'll be the chick.
Did I get it?
Thank you very much.
So, thank you all for watching today.
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
Did you have a good time?
We had a lot of fun too.
Please take this opportunity to check out the many special offers we have for you.
Please take this opportunity to check it out.
So, thank you very much for watching our webcast.
Thank you very much.
See you again soon.
Let's still have fun together this summer.
Let's have fun.
And please tweet about the hashtag benefit Armon.
Please do.
So, lock on to your hearts!
That's all for us.
Jou! It was a thrilling senlove.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
See you soon.
Oh, no, Moon.
Bye-bye.
I love, love, love.
He even gave me that look.
He's so cute.
He said he was right on top of you.
So cute.
Where are you going today?
When are you coming home?
Soon today.Soon today.
Worried about
I love you
Cute cute cute cute
cute cute cute cute
Good night
Good night, sweetie.
Good night, sweetheart.
Good night.
Good night.Good night.
Thank you for watching
After this, when I am at my house, when I am at my house, when I am at my house, when I am at my house, when I am at my house, when I am at my house, when I am at my house, when I am at my house When I am at my house, when I am at my house, when I am at my house, when I am at my house, when I am at my house, when I am at my house, when I am at my house, when I am at my house, when I am at my house, when I am at my house, when I am at my house, when I am at my house, when I am at my house
came.
Thank you for watching